poecraft.com 2019-06-20

# Privacy Policy

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their "Personally Identifiable Information" (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website. 

**What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?**

We do not collect personally identifiable information on this website. Personally identifiable information will never be requested on this website. 

**What do we collect?**

We may collect the following information when registering: 

  * Third-party usernames and IDs
  * OpenID / OAuth Identifiers
  * IP Addresses

This information is only collected and used to create or modify a personal account on this website. When registering, you agree that your third-party username may be exposed on this website via your profile or posts. 

We do collect logs from actions performed when browsing and interacting with the website, such as saving information to the site. Such logs may contain which pages were requested, when they were requested, and what IP address they were requested from. 

**When do we collect information?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site or enter information on our site applications. 

**How do we use your information?**

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways: 

  * To improve our website in order to better serve you and other users.
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
  * To identify and prevent abuse of services and other malicious activities.

**How do we protect your information?**

We never ask for personal or private information like names, email addresses, or credit card numbers. Third party data stored on this website is only used to identify you to access account data on this website. The only non-sensitive third-party usernames and identifiers will ever be made public, if exposed at all. 

**Do we use "cookies" and "local storage"?**

Yes. We use cookies to store account login information and site settings. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future (possibly through third parties). 

We also store information on your computer as "local storage," which utilizes a browsers web storage functionality. This saved information includes personal settings and information specific to the user. This browser webstorage is utilized to enhance a user's specific experience within the website. This personal information is never sent to the server unless specifically requested by the user. 

**We use cookies to:**

  * Save user's login information and preferences for future visits.
  * Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf such as Google Analytics. 

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. 

**If users disable cookies in their browser:**

If you turn cookies off, some of site features may not function properly. You might not have access to certain personal account features. 

**Third-party disclosure**

As we do not collect PII, we do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when it's release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property or safety. 

**Third-party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

**Google**

Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en 

We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy. 

**We have implemented the following:**

**Opting out:**

Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page or by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on. 

**California Online Privacy Protection Act**

CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require any person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting Personally Identifiable Information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals or companies with whom it is being shared. - See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf 

**According to CalOPPA, we agree to the following:**

  * Users can visit our site anonymously. Entering information is completely optional.
  * Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum, on the first significant page after entering our website.
  * Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy' and can easily be found on the page specified above.

Any changes to our Privacy Policy may be found on this page.

**How does our site handle Do Not Track signals?**

We honor Do Not Track signals and do not track any personally identifiable or behavioral information when a DNT request is sent to our website. 

**Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?**

We do not directly use any first-party behavioral tracking. There may be third party behavioral tracking in our third-party services, such as Google reCAPTCHA and Adsense. Google's privacy policy can be found [here.](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/)
